Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 4: Broadcast Center Recordings, 2000 January 14-2009 December 17; 40 boxes
  - Keith Whittington, 2007 May 02; 796; 1 box (Box 21)
    Political Foundations of Judicial Supremacy: The Presidency, the Supreme Court, and Constitutional Leadership in US History, Moderator - Robert George, Panelists - Stanley Brubaker, Mark Graber, Ken Kersch, Keith Whittington Bowl 2 Robertson Hall
  - Dr. Glenn N. Cummings, 2007 May 08; 797; 1 box (Box 21)
    Dr. Glenn N. Cummings - Medical School Admissions Lecture
    Health Professions Advising
  - What is Prayer?, 2007 May 11; 955; 1 box (Box 23)
    CSR Symposium - 5/11/2007 What is Prayer? An Interdisciplinary Symposium: Sister Mary Margaret Funk, David Hall, Albert Raboteau and Carol Zaleski
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 14; 788; 1 box (Box 20)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - Carson Holloway, Panelists - Stanley Kurtz, Peter Augustine, Alan Levine, Michael Zuckert Panel 1 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 14; 789; 1 box (Box 20)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - George Dent, Jr., Panelists - Gerard Bradley, Michael Krauss, Jack Wade Nowlin, Amy Wa Tape 2 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 14; 790; 1 box (Box 20)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - John Mueller, Panelists - Benjamin Barber, Stanley Brubaker, Charles Griswold Tape 3 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 14; 791; 1 box (Box 20)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges - Keynote Address, John Agresto Tape 4 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - OIT Meeting, 2007 May 14; 795; 1 box (Box 21)
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 15; 792; 1 box (Box 20)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - Bradley Watson, Panelists - William Allen, Angelo Codevilla, Matthew Franck, Alan Gibson, John Lenczowski Tape 5 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 15; 793; 1 box (Box 21)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - Robert George, Panelists - Hadley Arkes, Charles Butterworth, David Novak, James Stoner, Jr. Tape 6 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, 2007 May 15; 794; 1 box (Box 21)
    The Free Society: Foundations and Challenges, Moderator - Steven Bullock, Panelists - Herman Belz, Joyce Lee Malcolm, Paul Moreno, Darren Staloff Tape 7 of 7 Bowen Hall
  - Carlo Petrini, 2007 May 17; 798; 1 box (Box 21)
    Carlo Petrini - Slow Food Nation McCosh 50
    CES
  - Dana Gioia, 2007 November 03; 834; 1 box (Box 21)
    Writers, Editors, and Literary Magazines, 1947-2007 Welcome: Shirley Tilghman, Keynote Address: Dana Gioia, Panelists: Anthony Grafton, Lea Carpenter, Paula Deitz, Emily Grosholz, David Orr, William Pritchard, Michael Wood, Sean Wilentz 185 Nassau Street
    Rare Books
  - Carlos Eire, 2007 November 06; 840; 1 box (Box 21)
    A Brusque History of Eternity 1 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Susan Wolf, 2007 November 07; 835; 1 box (Box 21)
    Meaning In Life And Why It Matters -Susan Wolf, Robert Adams, John Koethe
  - Carlos Eire, 2007 November 07; 841; 1 box (Box 21)
    A Brusque History of Eternity 2 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Susan Wolf, 2007 November 08; 836; 1 box (Box 21)
    Meaning In Life And Why It Matters -Susan Wolf, Nomy Arpaly, Jonathan Haidt
  - ASPIRE Press Conference, 2007 November 08; 837; 1 box (Box 21)
    Shirley Tilghman, Robert Murley, Nancy Peretsman
  - Carlos Eire, 2007 November 08; 842; 1 box (Box 21)
    A Brusque History of Eternity 3 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Jonathan Cohen, 2007 November 09; 839; 1 box (Box 21)
    Neuroscience at Princeton
    Development
  - The Future of the Internet, 2007 November 09; 843; 1 box (Box 21)
    Moderator: Eric Schmidt Õ76, Edward W. Felten, Larry L. Peterson, Jennifer L. Rexford Õ91, Introduction: Donald R. Dixon Õ69 McCosh 50 1:30 pm
  - What It Means to Be Human, 2007 November 09; 844; 1 box (Box 21)
    Kwame Anthony Appiah, Jonathan D. Cohen, Introduction: Kathryn A. Hall Õ80 McCosh 10 1:30 pm
  - Climate Change: Science and Solutions, 2007 November 09; 845; 1 box (Box 21)
    Michael Oppenheimer, Stephen W. Pacala, H. Vincent Poor *77 Introduction: Kimberly E. Ritrievi McCosh 50 3:00 pm
  - Shaping a Writer, 2007 November 09; 846; 1 box (Box 21)
    A. Scott Berg '71, Jeffrey K. Eugenides, John A. McPhee '53, David J. Remnick Õ81 McCosh 10 3:00 pm
  - Sydney Johnson, 2007 November 10; 838; 1 box (Box 21)
    Sydney Johnson
  - Atul Gawande, 2007 November 13; 849; 1 box (Box 21)
    Mediocrity and Its Causes: A Surgeon's Notes on Medical Performance
  - Aref Chowdury, 2007 November 19; 902; 1 box (Box 22)
    Nonlinearities in Positive and Negative Refractive Index Media
    EE
  - David Remnick, 2007 November 20; 850; 1 box (Box 21)
    A Conversation with David Remnick - Hosted by Professor Michael Wood
  - The Genius of James Brown, 2007 November 29; 851; 1 box (Box 21)
    Ain't That A Groove: The Genius of James Brown, Moderator: Daphne Brooks, Panelist: Robert Christgau, Farah Griffin, Alan Leeds, Fred Moten Richardson
  - Cristian Samper, 2007 October 03; 808; 1 box (Box 21)
    Smithsonian Institution McDonnell Auditorium A02
  - Thomas L. Pangle, 2007 October 04; 806; 1 box (Box 21)
    The Great Debate: The Federalist Response to the Anti-Federalist Challenge - Thomas L. Pangle Friend 006
  - Daphne Brooks, 2007 October 06; 812; 1 box (Box 21)
    Fall Football Lecture: "Bring the Pain: The Politics of Black Comedy and Satire in the Post-Civil Rights Era" McCormick Hall
  - Dan Vittorio Segre, 2007 October 08; 807; 1 box (Box 21)
    The Rise and Fall of Italian Jewry From 1839-1939 and the Revival of Italian Judaism in Italy and Israel Dan Vittorio Segre East Pyne 010
  - Paula Fredriksen, 2007 October 09; 826; 1 box (Box 21)
    Sin: The Early History of an Idea 1 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Paula Fredriksen, 2007 October 10; 827; 1 box (Box 21)
    Sin: The Early History of an Idea 2 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Paula Fredriksen, 2007 October 11; 828; 1 box (Box 21)
    Sin: The Early History of an Idea 3 of 3 McCosh 10
  - Anthony M. Esolen, 2007 October 15; 829; 1 box (Box 21)
    Dante and Freedom: The Autonomy of Hell and The Liberty of Paradise
  - James Piereson, 2007 October 17; 830; 1 box (Box 21)
    Revisiting President John F. Kennedy and the 1960s Friend 006
  - Carlos Fuentes, 2007 October 18; 831; 1 box (Box 21)
    A Panoramic View of the History of Mexico McCosh 10
  - Carlos Brody, 2007 October 24; 832; 1 box (Box 21)
    Tiger Talk - Is There a Mathematician in Your Brain?Richardson Auditorium
  - Paul Starr, 2007 October 25; 833; 1 box (Box 21)
    Freedom's Power: The True Force of Liberalism Moderator: Kim Lane Scheppele, Panelists: Paul Starr, E.J. Dionne Jr., James Ceaser, Jennifer Hochschild, Peter Berkowitz CS 104
  - F. A. Dahlen Memorial Service, 2007 September 07; 804; 1 box (Box 21)
    F. A. Dahlen Memorial Service Start Dub at 2:30 Chapel
  - Bonnie Bassler, 2007 September 09; 820; 1 box (Box 21)
    Freshman Assembly Lecture - Molecular Language: Evolutionary Enabler McCarter Theater
  - Reflections on Diversity, 2007 September 11; 805; 1 box (Box 21)
    Reflections on Diversity McCarter Theater
  - Sex On A Saturday Night, 2007 September 15; 814; 1 box (Box 21)
    Sex On A Saturday Night Richardson
  - Daniel Gilbert, 2007 September 20; 813; 1 box (Box 21)
    How To Do Precisely the Right Thing at All Possible Times
  - OIT Meeting, 2007 September 24; 811; 1 box (Box 21)
    Princeton University. Office of Information Technology
  - Demetri Porphyrios, 2007 September 26; 809; 1 box (Box 21)
    Tradition and Modernity: The Making of Whitman College
    Development Events
  - Larry Bartels, 2007 September 29; 810; 1 box (Box 21)
    Fall Football Lecture: "Economic Inequality and American Democracy" McCormick Hall, Room 101 at 11:00 a.m.
  - Marc Rosen '98, 2008 March 28; 898; 1 box (Box 62)
    Marc Rosen '98; Career Services
  - Josh Marshall, 2008 April 01; 900; 1 box (Box 22)
    Josh Marshall and Professor Anthony Grafton - The Current Political Scene
  - Dom Juan, 2008 April 03; 901; 1 box (Box 22)
    11 minutes of Footage of McCosh 50 at the front of tape, then color bars, then performance starts 2 mins in from color bars
    L'Atelier
  - Eric Dunham, 2008 April 07; 903; 1 box (Box 22)
    Earth Modeling From Fault Friction to Seismic Hazard
    Geosciences
  - Robert Alter, 2008 April 08; 904; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Bible and American Literature Part 1of 3: Moby-Dick: Polyphony
  - Robert Alter, 2008 April 09; 905; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Bible and American Literature Part 2 of 3: Absalom, Absalom!: Lexicon
  - Robert Alter, 2008 April 10; 906; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Bible and American Literature Part 3 of 3: Seize the Day: American Amalgam
  - Princeton Preview, 2008 April 10; 908; 1 box (Box 22)
    President Tilghman Richardson
  - SEAS Princeton Preview, 2008 April 11; 909; 1 box (Box 22)
    SEAS Princeton Preview
    Undergraduate Affairs C209
  - Michael Celia *83, 2008 April 15; 908; 1 box (Box 22)
    Alumni Association Maclean House Lecture The Importance of Carbon Burial in Electricity Generation Professor Michael Celia *83 Civil and Environmental Engineering Program Audio Channel 2
  - Muslim Philanthropy in Transition, 2008 April 17; 910; 1 box (Box 22)
    Muslim Philanthropy in Transition - Prospects and Challenges by Ebrahim Moosa Second Annual Doll Family Lecture on Religion and Money April 17, 2008 Betts Auditorium
    Religion
  - Princeton Preview, 2008 April 17; 911; 1 box (Box 22)
  - Jeanne Guillemin, 2008 April 18; 907; 1 box (Box 22)
    Between Terrorism and Indifference: Charting the Future of Biodefense Policy
    Program on Science and Global Security
  - SEAS Princeton Preview, 2008 April 18; 912; 1 box (Box 22)
  - Ian Garrick-Bethell, 2008 April 21; 913; 1 box (Box 22)
    Lunar Tidal Geodynamics
  - John Prendergast, 2008 April 21; 914; 1 box (Box 22)
    Crystal Tiger Award
  - Mario Vargas Llosa, 2008 April 22; 915; 1 box (Box 22)
    Onetti and the Shadows of Faulkner and Borges
  - Peter Folb, 2008 April 25; 916; 1 box (Box 22)
    Project Coast: South Africa's Apartheid-Era Chemical and Biological Warfare Program, and its Implications for Scientific Research and Global Health Security
    PSGS
  - Insight into Leadership, 2008 April 26; 917; 1 box (Box 22)
    William Russel and Nannerl Keohane 1 of 4 Wallace 300
    Alumni Relations
  - Insight into Leadership, 2008 April 26; 918; 1 box (Box 22)
    Lisa Drakeman, Morton Collins, Burton Malkiel 2 of 4 Wallace 300
  - Insight into Leadership, 2008 April 26; 919; 1 box (Box 22)
    Ravi Sethi, Laurence Morse, Ann Kirschner 3 of 4 Wallace 300
  - Insight into Leadership, 2008 April 26; 920; 1 box (Box 22)
    Wesley Harris, Neil Rudenstine, Donald Drakeman 4 of 4 Wallace 300
  - Robert Goheen, 2008 April 27; 921; 1 box (Box 22)
    Service of Remembrance and Celebration Chapel
    VP and Secretary
  - OIT Groundbreaking Video, 2008 June 30; 1077; 1 box (Box 56)
    OIT Groundbreaking October 2008; OIT
  - Vangimalla Reddy, 2008 September 22; 2156; 1 box (Box 66)
    Climate Change and Crop Productivity: Challenges and Opportunities
  - The Brain, 2008 September 23; 2150; 1 box (Box 66)
    Barry Jacobs
  - Ellen Baum, 2008 September 29; 2089; 1 box (Box 63)
    Navigating the Science: Mitigating Options and Climate Politics of Black Carbon
  - The Brain, 2008 October 21; 2153; 1 box (Box 66)
  - The Brain, 2008 October 07; 2151; 1 box (Box 66)
  - The Brain, 2008 October 14; 2152; 1 box (Box 66)
  - The Brain, 2008 November 18; 2154; 1 box (Box 66)
  - The Brain, 2008 November 11; 2155; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Joel Schwartz, 2008 November 03; 2142; 1 box (Box 65)
    Dust Kills: From Combustion, Practices, and Genes to Policy
  - CK Rao, 2008 November 10; 2145; 1 box (Box 66)
    Biosecurity Regulation of Genetically Engineered Crops in India: An Analysis of Science, Policy, and Anti-GE Activism
  - Andrew Delbanco, 2008 December 03; 2180; 1 box (Box 67)
    3 of 3
  - Frank Dentener, 2008 December 08; 2091; 1 box (Box 63)
    Climate Change and Air Pollution: Regional and Global Analyses of the Benefits and Tradeoffs of Emission Reduction Options
  - David Wilcove, 2008 December 01; 2148; 1 box (Box 66)
    The Impacts of Agriculture on Biodiversity: Lessons and Lies from Kenya and Borneo
  - David Eyton, 2008 October 13; 2092; 1 box (Box 63)
    Energy Challenges for the 21st Century- An International Company Perspective
  - Andrew Dobson, 2008 October 20; 2095; 1 box (Box 64)
    Quantitative Glimpses of Four Emerging Pathogens
  - Philippe Benoit, 2008 October 06; 2130; 1 box (Box 65)
    Energy and Climate: A World Bank Perspective
  - Ashish Kothari, 2008 November 24; 2133; 1 box (Box 65)
    India's Economic Miracle and the Crisis of Environmental Governance
  - J. Timmons Roberts, 2008 November 17; 2135; 1 box (Box 65)
    Greening Aid: Understanding the Environmental Impact of Development Assistance
  - Marcia Angell, 2008 September 17; 969; 1 box (Box 56)
    Public Lecture in McCosh 50 w simulcast. Dept of Social Medicine Lecture; Public Lectures
  - How to Make Complex Science Compelling, 2008 September 23; 1097; 1 box (Box 56)
    Dean for Research/Communications; Part 2; Office of Communications
  - Lord Griffiths, 2008 September 24; 976; 1 box (Box 56)
    Doing God in 10 Downing Street': The Relationship Between Faith and Politics in a Postmodern World; Center for the Study of Religion
  - Jeanne Mrak, 2008 November 20; 1045; 1 box (Box 56)
    Office 2007 Firestone Library/Human Resources Office 2007; Library Human Resources
  - Leonard Susskind, 2008 November 20; 1050; 1 box (Box 56)
    The Black Hole War; Physics
  - Facilities Vista Upgrade Project, 2008 December 10; 1073; 1 box (Box 56)
    Facilities Vista Upgrade Project; Facilities
  - Andrew Delbanco, 2008 December 01; 1056; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Does College Really Matter? The History of Undergraduate Education, Why It's in Trouble, and What to Do About It"
  - Cornel West, 2008 December 01; 1057; 1 box (Box 48)
    African American Studies 201
  - Joshua Kun, 2008 December 01; 1065; 1 box (Box 48)
    "All You Shall Know Us by the Trail of Our Vinyl: Music, Memory, and the Politics of Jewish-American History"
    Program in American Studies
  - Arthur Caplan, Robert P. George, Eric S. Gregory, Robert Jensen, 2008 December 01; 1075; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Being Human in the Age of Technology: A Discussion of Eric Cohen's New Book 'In the Shadow of Progress'"
  - Andrew Delbanco, 2008 December 02; 1055; 1 box (Box 48)
    Public Lecture
  - Warren Powell, 2008 December 02; 1063; 1 box (Box 48)
    Engineering Communications Interview
    Engineering Communications
  - Maria Garlock, 2008 December 02; 1064; 1 box (Box 48)
  - Guthrie Ramsey, Jr, 2008 December 03; 1061; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Made in America: The History of Black Gospel Music" Gospel Choir
  - Cornel West, 2008 December 03; 1062; 1 box (Box 48)
    AAS 201 Lecture
  - Professor Talal Asad, 2008 December 04; 1068; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Thinking About Religion, Belief, and Politics"
    Princeton university. Department of religion
  - Collin Jackson, 2008 December 04; 1082; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Extracting Passwords from JavaScript Password Managers"
    Princeton University. Center for Information Technology Policy
  - Jacque Fletcher, 2008 December 05; 1060; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Crime in a Wheat Field: Forensic Plant Pathology, A New Discipline to Meet National Needs
  - 2008 Princeton Sports Symposium, 2008 December 05; 1069; 1 box (Box 48)
    Part 1/3: Athletic Marketing and Representation
    ODUS- Princeton Sports Symposium
  - 2008 Princeton Sports Symposium, 2008 December 05; 1070; 1 box (Box 48)
    Part 2/3: Professional and Amateur Sports Properties
  - 2008 Princeton Sports Symposium, 2008 December 05; 1071; 1 box (Box 48)
    Part 3/3: The Olympic Games
  - Center for African American Studies- AAS 201, 2008 December 08; 1072; 1 box (Box 48)
  - Douglas Laycock, 2008 December 08; 1074; 1 box (Box 48)
    "The Religious Exemptions Debate"
  - Cornel West, 2008 December 10; 1086; 1 box (Box 48)
    AAS 201
  - Edward Tenner, 2008 December 12; 1081; 1 box (Box 48)
    "Biosecurity, Biotechnology, and Global Health"
  - The Social Costs of Pornography, 2008 December 12; 1098; 1 box (Box 48)
    Speaker: Norman Doidge; event hosted by Professor Robert George
  - The Social Costs of Pornography Session 1, 2008 December 12; 1100; 1 box (Box 48)
    Speakers: Roger Scruton, Pamela Paul; event hosted by Professor Robert George
  - The Social Costs of Pornography Session 4, 2008 December 12; 1101; 1 box (Box 48)
    Speakers: Ana Bridges, Kirk Doran; event hosted by Professor Robert George
  - Nancy Pelosi, 2008 December 15; 1080; 1 box (Box 48)
    Innovation Roundtable: Renewing Our National Commitment to the Physical Sciences and Energy Research - The Honorable Nancy Pelosi, President Shirley Tilghman, The Honorable Rush Holt, Mr. Norman Augustine
  - Libex Demo, 2008 December 16; 1088; 1 box (Box 48)
    Libex Demo and Talk in Firestone Library
    Library (Human Resources)
  - Andlinger Lecture, 2008 December 18; 1087; 1 box (Box 48)
    Andlinger Lecture Engineering Communications
  - Krista Tippett, 2008 February 05; 862; 1 box (Box 21)
    Krista Tippett - Speaking of Faith Panel Discussion
  - Election 2008: Where Do Things Go from Here? Conservative Perspectives, 2008 February 06; 863; 1 box (Box 21)
    Moderator: Robert P. George Panelists: William Kristol, Eric Cohen, James W. Ceaser, Yuval Levin, Aaron Burr 219
  - Robert McCauley, 2008 February 07; 864; 1 box (Box 21)
    The Role of Maturationally Natural Cognition in Science and Religion Jones 100
  - Evangelicalism and Politics in America, 2008 February 08; 865; 1 box (Box 21)
    Panelists: Michael Hout Robin Rogers-Dillon Melani McAlister East Pyne 101
  - Diana Schaub, 2008 February 11; 868; 1 box (Box 22)
    Bioethics: What Would the Founders Say? Aaron Burr 219
  - David Suzuki, 2008 February 12; 866; 1 box (Box 21)
    David Suzuki Start Dub at 4 min 30 sec DVD Master of lecture exists, use it for dubbing McCosh 50
  - Youndsuk Chi, 2008 February 12; 867; 1 box (Box 22)
    Conversation with Youndsuk Chi Audio from camera mic, recorded low, boost when dubbing Robertson 02
    Princeton University. Career Services
  - Jason Weir, 2008 February 18; 869; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Origin of the Latitudinal Diversity Gradient Guyot 10
    EEB
  - Carl Tape, 2008 February 18; 870; 1 box (Box 22)
    Seismic Tomography of Southern California Using Adjoint Methods Guyot 220
  - Eric Tytell, 2008 February 19; 871; 1 box (Box 22)
    From Vortices to Neurons and Back Again Guyot 10
  - Jonathan Sarna, 2008 February 20; 872; 1 box (Box 22)
    Jonathan Sarna on "The Democratization of American Judaism" McCormick 101
    American Studies
  - Robert Haas, 2008 February 21; 873; 1 box (Box 22)
    Robert Haas Poetry Reading McCormick 101
    Center for Visitor and Conference Services
  - Jon Hlafter, 2008 February 23; 878; 1 box (Box 22)
    A Conversation with Jon Hlafter McCosh 50
  - Robinson Wally Fulweiler, 2008 February 25; 874; 1 box (Box 22)
    Climate Induced Changes of Benthic Pelagic in Narragansett Bay, RI Guyot 10
  - David Ma, 2008 February 25; 876; 1 box (Box 22)
    Collapse Analysis of Framed Structures Under Extreme Conditions Bowen 222
    Princeton University. Department of Civil and Environmental Engineering
  - Andrea Graham, 2008 February 26; 875; 1 box (Box 22)
    Effector Immunology Guyot 10
  - The Open Campus, 2008 February 26; 877; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Open Campus: A Conversation about the Changing Nature of Campuses and Campus Planning Henry N. Cobb, Robert Geddes, Frances Halsband, Guy Nordenson, Denise Scott Brown, Moderator: Neil Kittredge
  - Andrea Jung, 2008 February 26; 907; 1 box (Box 22)
    The IMAGINE Speaker Series presents Andrea Jung '79, CEO of Avon Products, Inc
  - Vatican II, 2008 February 28; 960; 1 box (Box 23)
    Vatican II - A Sociological Analysis of Religious Change - A symposium on the work of Melissa J. Wilde
  - King Abdullah II of Jordan, 2008 February 29; 879; 1 box (Box 22)
    King Abdullah II of Jordan Richardson
  - The Opportunity of Crisis: Integrating the University of Alabama, 2008 February 29; 880; 1 box (Box 22)
    Moderators: Sean Wilentz and Valerie Smith; Panelists: Bob Drew, John Doar, Nicholas Katzenbach, D.A. Pennebaker
  - Nicholas Stern, 2008 January 07; 854; 1 box (Box 21)
    Economy and Climate Change McCosh 50
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 14; 855; 1 box (Box 21)
    Survey Talk by Ed Felten Tape 1 of 6 Friend Convo Room
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 14; 856; 1 box (Box 21)
    Possession and Ownership of Data: Moderator - Ed Felten, Panelists - Joel Reidenberg, Timothy Lee, Marc Rotenberg Tape 2 of 6 Friend Convo Room
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 14; 857; 1 box (Box 21)
    Security and Risk in the Cloud: Alex Halderman - Moderator, Panelists - Marc Hedlund, Mihai Christodorescu, Benjamin Mako Hill Tape 3 of 6
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 15; 858; 1 box (Box 21)
    Harlan Yu - Princeton Research Presentation: Estimating Web Traffic Using DNS Cache Tape 4 of 6 Friend Convo Room
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 15; 859; 1 box (Box 21)
    Civics in the Cloud: Moderator - David Robinson, Panelists - Josh Tauberer, Andrew Page, John Wonderlich Tape 5 of 6 Friend Convo Room
  - Computing in the Cloud, 2008 January 15; 860; 1 box (Box 21)
    What's Next? Moderator: Andrea LaPaugh, Panelists: Reihan Salam, Jesse Robbins, Jonathan Rochelle Tape 6 of 6 Friend Convo Room
  - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, 2008 January 21; 861; 1 box (Box 21)
    Address by Jose Huizar CASYM Steel Orchestra
  - Baccalaureate 2008, 2008 June 01; 949; 1 box (Box 23)
    Baccalaureate 2008
  - Class Day 2008, 2008 June 02; 950; 1 box (Box 23)
    Class Day 2008
  - Hooding Ceremony 2008, 2008 June 02; 951; 1 box (Box 23)
    Hooding Ceremony 2008
  - Commencement 2008, 2008 June 03; 952; 1 box (Box 23)
    Commencement 2008
  - Craig Miller, 2008 March 03; 881; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Genetic Basis of Evolutionary Change
  - Blair Schoene, 2008 March 03; 883; 1 box (Box 22)
  - Siobain Duffy, 2008 March 04; 882; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Evolutionary Genetics and Genomics of Emerging Viruses
  - Alexander Nehamas, 2008 March 04; 884; 1 box (Box 22)
    "Because It Was He, Because It Was I" The Good of Friendship
  - Jin Hyung Lee, 2008 March 05; 886; 1 box (Box 22)
    Meeting the Technical Challenges for Functional and Molecular MRI
    Princeton University. Department of Electrical Engineering
  - Sigrid Adriaenssens, 2008 March 06; 887; 1 box (Box 22)
    Form Follows Force
  - Branko Glisic, 2008 March 07; 888; 1 box (Box 22)
    Fiber Optic Methods for Structural Health Monitors
  - Wonsuck Kim, 2008 March 10; 889; 1 box (Box 22)
    The Pulse of Calm Fan Delta
  - Peter Andolfalto, 2008 March 10; 890; 1 box (Box 22)
    Constraint and Adaptive Evolution in the Drosophila Genome
  - Dr. Luke Theogarajan, 2008 March 11; 891; 1 box (Box 22)
    Bio-ionic Neural Interfaces
  - Terrence Taylor, 2008 March 14; 892; 1 box (Box 22)
    Countering Biological Risks
  - Stephen Parman, 2008 March 17; 893; 1 box (Box 22)
    Crustal Growth, Catastrophic Mantle Melting Events and Evolution of the Atmosphere Biosphere System
  - Chloe Michaut, 2008 March 24; 894; 1 box (Box 22)
    Volcanism and Evolution of Terrestrial Planets
  - Edwidge Danticat, 2008 March 25; 895; 1 box (Box 22)
    Create Dangerously: The Immigrant Artist at Work